wards.com 2007-06-09

# Privacy Policy

**Montgomery Ward Privacy Policy**

We understand and share your concern about privacy and value the trust you place in us. Montgomery Ward wants to assure you that we respect your privacy and confidentiality and take great care to safeguard your personal information. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices. If you have any questions regarding this policy, please click here to send us an email.

**Information We Collect**  
We recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect to make products and services more efficient for you and to communicate with you about products, services and promotions.

**Automatic Information Tracking**  
We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on our site. We use this information to analyze our user’s behavior and interests to better understand and serve our customer. This information may include the IP address of your computer, your browser software and operating system, information about your viewing, search and purchase history and information about the referring URL and the URL clickstream to, through and from our Web sites. We do not automatically capture your email address or any personally identifiable information unless your provide that information in conjunction with a request for information or by placing an order with us.

**Cookies**  
We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart and identify how a customer found our website. Cookies are never used to store sensitive information such as names, addresses, credit card numbers or passwords.

**Our Use of Your Information**  
We use the information we collect to improve our services and products and make your shopping experience more efficient and relevant.

**E-mails**  
It is possible to register as a Montgomery Ward email subscriber directly from our site. Upon registering, we will periodically send you e-mail newsletters and e-mails featuring sales, promotions and other member-only benefits.

**Unsubscribe**  
If you would rather not receive emails, please click here to unsubscribe your email address form any future communication. You may also call us at 1-800-227-7598, or write to us at the address below to be removed from our email or catalog mailing lists.

**Affiliate Programs**  
Our affiliate program is administered by LinkShare. Any information collected by LinkShare is not governed by this policy.

**Sharing Your Information with Third Parties**  
If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive mailings from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by sending us an email, calling us at 1-800-227-7598, or writing to us at the address provided below. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed with us. 

Telephone numbers and email addresses are never shared with third parties unless specific permission is given to do so.

**Security**  
We utilize industry-standard SSL encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. 

**Changes to This Policy**  
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will use for these new purposes only data collected after the change in policy is posted on this web site.

**Contacting Montgomery Ward**  
We welcome your feedback. If you have questions or comments about our privacy policies, feel free to contact us by:

**Email:**  
Click here to send us an email.

**By Mail:**  
Montgomery Ward  
P.O. Box 2789  
Cedar Rapids, IA 52406 

**Phone:** 1-800-227-7598

**Fax:** 1-319-896-5820

If you have other questions, please click here to send email to our customer service department, or call us at 1-800-227-7598.
